In a world of Heroes
and Villains
one power ruled all Black Adam
has been asleep for 5,000 years
we are here to negotiate your
peaceful surrender I am not peaceful
nor do I surrender
my powers are not a gift
but a curse
born of rage
You have two choices . You can be the destroyer of this world. Or it can be, it is savior.
It is his darkness that allows him to do what heroes cannot.
The battle you're meant to fight is upon us
there's no one on this planet that can stop me
Welcome everyone I'm Charlie this will be
my new Black Adam trailer video, they released a
Black Adam Justice League Trailer, there's a
ton of footage we'll break it all down if you're
new to the channel the movie is coming out
very soon i'll make videos for it like i do
for all the other great movies make sure you subscribe
to get them. I'm doing a raffle for movie tickets.
when we zoom in a little bit closer obviously
this new trailer is a big black adam against
the justice league typographical trailer like they're
leaning heavily on the association between black adam
character in justice league four
important reasons i will explain some of you have been
thinking about this ever since
the black adam movie was announced but the other funny thing that may have
what just happened is that when they released
the promo they actually removed the official one.
the promo changed it a little bit like they did a
new edit and then reuploaded it the rock even
posted corrected so when it says corrected what it
means is that the original version of the promo had a
scene from the Joss Whedon version from the Justice
League movie and they just re-released one without her
the footage they removed was basically like
a scene from Joss Whedon's version of Steppenwolf
swinging his ax and I guess people went crazy for
that I didn't actually see people coming to
complain about it i only saw it after they reuploaded the new one
it actually took me a little while to figure it out
what had happened like wait a minute why did
they reupload it what was wrong with the first one it
turns out that there was a bunch
of theatrical Justice League footage that people just
really didn't like they basically just cut it out
and then re-uploaded it Warner Brothers
said something weird about it e not using
snyder cut footage in a lot of their current movies like
that is why you don't see a lot
of snyder cut stuff within the actual upcoming movies a
lot of the movies reference other movies like
yagadas wonder woman actually film new scenes
for Shazam Fury the Gods like she's in that movie as
well and I think the
main reason the reason they don't use a lot of cut footage of Snyder in
their promos is particularly for financial
reasons that I think she has something to do with the
contracts between the two different versions
of Justice League and it's easier for them
at the corporate level not to address as just
dodge the issue but the other fun thing
they do during this Justice League promo is
they don't they included footage of the
actual Joker even though they're referencing him like they
included footage of Harley Quinn
blowing up chemicals here monkeys that were meant to be
she blew up the joker's hideout in the
birds of prey movie like it was a joker scene
without the real joker because it was meant to
be jared leto's joker and i think the reason
they did it because they're not totally
sure what they're going to do with the DC EU remake the
joker likes to make it sound like they don't want
to bring jared leto back as dceu joker so they're
gonna have to re-release at some point and
they're just not ready to do it yet because joaquin
phoenix is ​​joker the new
todd phillips joker sequel will probably blow up like
the first one and the fun of that is
he's meant to be in his own little universe
todd phillips has become so powerful because
his movies have been so successful in the first
The Joker movie was so successful that he and Joaquin
Phoenix got crazy contracts for the sequel so
basically they become so powerful that Warner
Brothers can't tell them you have to do it.
within the dceu like he doesn't cross over unless
Todd Phillips wants him to cross over it's the
same kind of thing with the Matt Reeves version of
Batman Robert Pattinson's Batman he wants
it to be like his own little separate universe
so they're protecting it even though they
just had all this
crazy corporate level stuff going on like the whole debacle with
the batgirl movie but the other big reason why they
released a black adam vs justice league
trailer kind of the Black Adam movie movie
is because currently the rock is releasing a
Black Adam versus Justice League movie that
I talked about earlier but now we just learned
a little bit more about it when they first announced that
the movie The Rock was making all these references
to Black Adam fighting a version of Henry Cavill's Superman
like he wanted to get a version of that
movie going but just for the way
things worked in the last two years,
it couldn't be the first movie, that's why Sabaka is
probably the villain of this first movie.
that it was just Superman because it would have
been a pretty awesome movie but during one of the
first promos they released for the actual movie
it literally put the Justice League on notice
as in the promo he specifically called them out
as if the hierarchy of DC EU was going to change
everyone has been posting memes on that line but
before I go I want you to help me with
something it's something that's pretty important
I need you to help me send a message to
uh some of the other some of the
other dc superheroes let's flash shazam
aquaman wonder woman batman and superman let them
know things will never be the same
because the hierarchy of power in
the dc universe is about to change
the funny thing about that is people it's
like why didn't he mention cyborg what is he?
going on with cyborg isn't he part of this
too who knows what's going on with that but
the reason he's doing that is because he's
trying to get interest in a black adam versus
justice league movie at dc reports recently that they
've been calling it Black Adam versus the
Justice League versus Suicide Squad it's kind
of a Mexican three-way matchup where I eat
each three separate forces even though Black Adam
doesn't technically have a team with him like he's
Black Adam for itself was the three
different forces in dceu kind of converge
and go against each other it looks like it's going to take
a while for him to figure out what he's going to do that
will eventually be and probably won't be the next
black adam movie that would be like the third or
fourth movie that they're working on, but that's the
main reason why they're seeing the rock talk
about the Justice League so much even though they're
featuring the So Justice Society during this movie
we will probably also see spin-offs
for the Justice Society at some point in the future.
the whole arc of the black adam movie is
the justice society convincing him to help them and
what will probably happen at the end of this first
movie is that he will end up defeating subak in
then just like in the comics the next
thing he will do is to take control of a conduct and rule it
with an Iron Fist and just kick out
everyone he doesn't like usually he only cares about himself
business and conduct ruling his own people
like he doesn't get involved in international affairs .
matters unless it involves some
larger magical problem potentially threatening behavior that
ends up happening in the story line they
tease in the first post-credits scene of the movie Shazam
with Mr Mind, the idea being that he wants to
use Dr. Savannah to take over the magical lands
Seven Kingdoms of magic that are like an
Alternate Dimension this is like pure magic if they
were able to make him become a powerful god
and threaten all of reality basically Black Adam
ended up getting involved in the arc of that comic book
so it looks like they're going to do it for the third time
shazam movie like they pay for that
post credit scene and black adam will get involved
in that and that's going to be his big
black adam vs shazam crossover but early prediction unless he
just sees completely to the left and do
something completely different than what they will do
is at the end of that
Black Adam Shazam crossover movie where they deal with Mr Mind in the Seven
Kingdoms of Magic is there's going to be some
bigger fallout that's going to affect the main Earth then
the Justice League is going to get involved and that's
what you're going to see Black Adam vs Justice League but
I think the whole Arc of that would be similar
to Arc of this first Black Adam movie where
as the Justice Society comes to try to win him over,
please help us, we know he doesn't like us, but we
need you to stop a bigger threat, only this
time it will be Superman who does it
as Superman he fights to a stop and as
he does so while they're busy beating up
the [ __ ] on each other all over the Earth he tries
to explain that you have to stop doing this there's a
bigger threat that we all have to come together
to fight that happened during the Justice is coming
a league movie like Darkseid and everybody has
to come together but like I said usually the only
time Black Adam gets involved as the
reason it would be a Black movie adam justice league is
because it's related to magic and speaking of henry
cavill coming back as superman someone actually
did a funny trailer edit of superman vs black
adam based on that recent black adam promo like
no one can stop me like oh no one except superman
there's no one on this planet that can stop me
if y'all didn't know too much henry cavill
has actually been using the management of The Rock
company for much of his business as an
actor that's why you see pictures of the two of them
together they're bros now , but there's also
business on the side that they have together so
the main idea right now is that The Rock
is trying to get this Black Adam vs.
Justice League movie down the road is the best
chance Henry Cavill has of coming back as
superman the other funny thing i didn't mention
earlier is if you realize that
justice league promo didn't include footage of the
flash i think for obvious reasons ways, better leave it.
that was kept under wraps until next year until they have to
market that movie out of sight but out of mind but
when it comes to the actual DC EU flash i think ezra
miller is out no matter how they release
the movie no they're going to take him out
or anything like that or remake the movie
in some way and after the movie comes out
he won't come back as The Flash in any big DC
projects like they'll just let the character sit
dormant for a while and then probably bring
in a recast version or bring in another flash
like Wally West I did a video a while ago about
this big 10 year plan that the CEO of Warner Brothers has
because of all these mergers that have been
going on the last two years we'll see what
ends up happening in the next few years, but it's
great to find out that The Rock really wants to
have more Justice League stuff in the
dceu I think of all the projects that are coming out
now between him and Shazam Fury of the Gods
those are like the best chance for the DCEU to
continue as you know it right now even though they're
probably going to reprise some of the
actors at some point some will stay
some will be recast and then some will be
Multiverse versions if there are any of the big easter eggs you
saw in the trailer something I didn't talk about
in the video or any other big questions
about Black Adam's future in the DCEU
just write it down in the comments my next one
big video will be episode 6 of House of the Dragon.
You can click here to update the link.
as soon as i post it and you can click here
to see all my other house of the dragon videos
Thank you so much for watching everyone
stay safe and I'll see you in the next one!